Tufts Daily Records UA176
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negatives, 1905 -- 2004; 1980 -- 2004; UA176.002; 5.0 Linear Feet
  - Sports, Fall and Spring, 2000 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001
    - Football vs. Williams, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00047; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Homecoming Football, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00048; Will (Box 20)
    - Homecoming Football, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00049; Will (Box 20)
    - Football v. Hamilton, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00050; Wittels (Box 20)
    - Football v. Hamilton, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00051; Wittels (Box 20)
    - Trinity vs. Tufts (Football and Soccer), 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00052; Katzenberg, Andrew (Box 20)
      Title and date from film form, year from binder; film form included
    - Trinity vs. Tufts (Football and Soccer), 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00053; Katzenberg, Andrew (Box 20)
    - Boston Marathon, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00054; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Boston Marathon, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00055; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Boston Marathon, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00056; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Boston Marathon, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00057; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Boston Marathon, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00058; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer (vs. Swarthmore), 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00059; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer (vs. Swarthmore), 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00060; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer (vs. Swarthmore), 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00061; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00062; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00063; Applebaum, Lauren (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00064; Applebaum, Lauren (Box 20)
      Roster included, film form included
    - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00065; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00066; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00067; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00068; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00069; Applebaum, Lauren (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Williams, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00070; Boudreau, L. (Box 20)
      Note and roster included
    - Men's Soccer vs. Williams, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00071; Boudreau, L. (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Colby, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00072; Kantor, Max Felkner (Box 20)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Colby, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00073; Kantor, Max Felkner (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00074; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer vs. Babson, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00075; Wittels (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer vs. Babson, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00076; Wittels (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer vs. Williams, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00077; Boudreau, L. (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer vs. Williams, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00078; Boudreau, L. (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00079; Kantor, Max Felkner (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00080; Kantor, Max Felkner (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00081; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00082; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00083; Tobel, Stephany (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00084; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00085; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, NCAA, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00086; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, NCAA, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00087; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Soccer, NCAA, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00088; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Cross Country, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00089; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Men's Cross Country, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00090; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Men's Cross Country, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00091; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Cross Country, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00092; Will (Box 20)
    - Cross Country, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00093 (Box 20)
    - Field Hockey, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00094; Kantor, Max Felkner (Box 20)
    - Field Hockey, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00095; Northeimer, Mary (Box 20)
    - Field Hockey vs. Wesleyan, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00096 (Box 20)
    - Field Hockey vs. Wesleyan, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00097 (Box 20)
    - Women's Field Hockey, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00098; Applebaum, Lauren (Box 20)
    - Women's Field Hockey, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00099; Applebaum, Lauren (Box 20)
    - Crew, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00100; Anderson, Katherine (Box 20)
    - Head of the Charles - Sailing/Crew, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00101; Sullivan, Laura (Box 20)
    - Intramurals, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00102; Wittels (Box 20)
    - Women's Rugby, 2000; UA176.002.020.00001.00103; Drop (Box 20)
    - Women's Rugby v. North Eastern, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00104; Wittels (Box 20)
    - Women's Rugby v. North Eastern, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00105; Wittels (Box 20)
    - Men's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00106; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00107; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00108; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00109; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00110; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00111; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00112; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00113; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00114; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball vs. Lasell, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00115; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00116; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00117; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00118; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00119; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00120; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00121; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00122; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball vs. CT College (and some cheerleading), 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00123; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball vs. CT College (and some cheerleading), 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00124; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00125; Applebaum, Lauren (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00126; Applebaum, Lauren (Box 20)
    - Women's Basketball, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00127; Applebaum, Lauren (Box 20)
    - Track and Field, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00128; Dunn, Lauren (Box 20)
    - Track, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00129; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Track, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00130; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Track, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00131; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Track and Field, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00132; Hendrickson, Christine (Box 20)
    - Track, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00133; Blaser, Evan (Box 20)
    - Men's Track, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00134; Leichman, Stephen (Box 20)
    - Men's Track, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00135; Leichman, Stephen (Box 20)
    - Tufts Track and Field, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00136; Hendrickson, Christine (Box 20)
    - Track, 2002 -- 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00137; Hendrickson, Christine (Box 20)
    - Hockey, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00138; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Hockey, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00139; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Hockey, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00140; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Hockey, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00141; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Ice Hockey, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00142; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Ice Hockey, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00143; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Ice Hockey, 2002; UA176.002.020.00001.00144; Boudreau, Laura (Box 20)
    - Men's Hockey, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00145; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Hockey, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00146; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Hockey, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00147; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 20)
    - Men's Squash, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00148; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Men's and Women's Squash, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00149; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Men's and Women's Squash, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00150; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
    - Men's and Women's Squash, 2003; UA176.002.020.00001.00151; Wittels, Will (Box 20)
  - Arts and Features, 2001 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00001
    - Features, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00001 (Box 21)
    - Changing Face of Tufts - Features, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00002; Odashima, Kay (Box 21)
      Note inlcuded
    - Peace and Justice, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00003; Hsu, Ray (Box 21)
    - Changes in Technology, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00004; Timble, Claire (Box 21)
    - Conversation between Blacks and Jews, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00005; Hsu, Ray (Box 21)
    - The Fours; Porter's Bar and Grille, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00006; Odashima, Kay (Box 21)
    - Comedy Show, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00007; Horak, Shana (Box 21)
    - Cambridge Commons, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00008; Kotwal, James (Box 21)
    - Godspell; Dress Rehearsal, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00009; Hsu, Ray (Box 21)
    - Features, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00010; Yen, Lesley Hue (Box 21)
    - Arts Haus, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00011; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Music Faculty Colloquium, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00012; Yen, Lesley Hue (Box 21)
    - Feminism, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00013; Souvanna, Phomdaen (Box 21)
    - TUSC Meeting, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00014; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 21)
    - Tufts Institute for the Environment, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00015; Timble, Claire (Box 21)
    - For Homecoming, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00016; Huna, Jeanette (Box 21)
    - Tufts on Wall Street, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00017; Souvanna, Phomdaen (Box 21)
    - Garden - Features, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00018; Timble, Claire (Box 21)
    - Tufts Online, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00019; Bui, Chloe (Box 21)
    - Wren Dorm (staircase), 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00020; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Club Hotung - Feature, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00021; Bedoya, A. (Box 21)
    - Tae Kwon Do - Features, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00022; Bedoya, Andrea (Box 21)
    - Dunkin' Donuts, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00023; Bedoya, A. (Box 21)
    - Pigeons in Davis Square, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00024; Turcan (Box 21)
    - Professor Joseph Hurka, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00025; Yen (Box 21)
    - Tapicha Stand at Porter, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00026; Bedoya (Box 21)
    - Wren Hall Bugs, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00027; Bedoya (Box 21)
    - Study Abroad, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00028; Churella (Box 21)
    - West Hall Quads, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00029; Bedoya (Box 21)
    - EPIIC Professor Teichman, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00001.00030; Hsu (Box 21)
      Date from binder, film form included
    - Cold Weather, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00001.00031; Hsu (Box 21)
    - Lord of the Rings, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00032; Hsu (Box 21)
    - Dell Laptop, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00033; Chester (Box 21)
    - LSAT, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00034; Taylor (Box 21)
    - Bored Students, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00035; DeBoer (Box 21)
    - Bored Students, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00036; DeBoer (Box 21)
    - Economics Department, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00001.00037; Taylor (Box 21)
    - Director of Financial Aid - Patricia Reilly, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00038; Hsu (Box 21)
    - Affirmative Action, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00039; Hsu (Box 21)
    - How students learn of news on Iraq and terrorism, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00040; Taylor (Box 21)
    - Hamilton Pool, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00041; Hsu (Box 21)
    - Kari McIntyre, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00042; Ferro (Box 21)
    - Marie McCool, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00043; Hsu (Box 21)
    - Roberta Oster Sachs-teaching her ex-college class, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00001.00044; Bedoya (Box 21)
    - Fraternity/Sorority Rush, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00045; Ferro (Box 21)
    - LGBT Center, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00046; Taylor (Box 21)
    - Director of Greek Life - Todd Sullivan, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00047; Hsu (Box 21)
    - Students at work - quitting/fired, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00048; Bedoya (Box 21)
    - Bartending, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00049; Bronesky (Box 21)
    - MBTA Red Line and Bus, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00050 (Box 21)
    - They're Going Places - Brandon Lucia, 2004; UA176.002.021.00001.00051; Beck (Box 21)
    - Playboy Magazine, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00001.00052; Bayer (Box 21)
    - Body Piercing, 2004; UA176.002.021.00001.00053; Darnayan, Sara (Box 21)
    - Jack Byrne at Comedy Vault, 2004; UA176.002.021.00001.00054; DeBoer, Jenny (Box 21)
    - Davis? Teele? Medford Square, 2004; UA176.002.021.00001.00055 (Box 21)
    - Reel Big Fish, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00056; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 21)
    - Dance Duet, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00057; Clampitt (Box 21)
    - Comedy Club at Elm St. Theatre, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00058; Hsu, Ray (Box 21)
    - Johnny D's Harvard Sq., 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00059; Northeimer, Mary (Box 21)
    - Hong Kong Bar, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00060; Turcan (Box 21)
    - Bands- 3 Day Threshold, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00061; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 21)
    - Aberden City at Carmichael Lounge, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00062; Luna (Box 21)
    - Arts, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00063; Yen, Lesley Hue (Box 21)
    - Diva Indian Restaurant, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00064; Yen, Hue (Box 21)
    - Bakowski's Tavern, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00065; Cieplak (Box 21)
    - Bars+ Clubs, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00066; Cieplak (Box 21)
    - Doug Fell Down at Oxfam, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00067; Cieplak (Box 21)
    - Acapella Homecoming Concert, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00068; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Ho Tung Concert, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00069; Felker (Box 21)
    - Ho Tung Concert, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00070; Felker, Max (Box 21)
    - Stage Assembly for Carmen, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00071; Lana (Box 21)
    - Bars in Davis Sq. Anna's Taqueria., 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00072; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 21)
    - Fall Fest, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00073; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 21)
    - Bombay Club, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00074; Wong (Box 21)
    - Faneuil Hall; Jose McIntyre's, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00075; Cieplak (Box 21)
    - Dorothy's Boutique, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00076; Berkowitz (Box 21)
    - Latino Culture, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00077; Clampitt (Box 21)
    - Dali Restaurant, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00078; Hsu (Box 21)
    - Tufts Orchestra Concert, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00079; Cieplak (Box 21)
    - Bhangra Rehearsal, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00080; O'Brien (Box 21)
    - Bhangra Competition, 2002; UA176.002.021.00001.00081; O'Brien (Box 21)
    - Merrin Lazyan, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00082; Odashima (Box 21)
    - Wang's Restaurant, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00083; Hayden (Box 21)
    - Brattle Theatre and Central Sq. T, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00084; Petrich (Box 21)
    - TASA Culture Show, 2001; UA176.002.021.00001.00085; Petrich (Box 21)
    - Caribbean Club Event, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00086; Petrich (Box 21)
    - Tufts Artist Marilinda Garcia, 2003; UA176.002.021.00001.00087; Burns (Box 21)
  - News, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00002
    - Sept. 11, 2002 Ceremony, UA176.002.021.00002.00001; Bedoya, Andrea (Box 21)
    - ID Cards; Green Line to Davis, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00002; Chapman, Andrew (Box 21)
    - US Senator; UCCPS, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00003; Hendrickson, Christine (Box 21)
    - Sept. 11, 2002, UA176.002.021.00002.00004; Hendrickson, C. (Box 21)
    - Sept. 11, 2002, UA176.002.021.00002.00005; Hendrickson, C. (Box 21)
    - 9/11 Flag Ceremony, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00006; Wittels (Box 21)
    - Engineering Diversity, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00007; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Maureen Harris, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00008; Chapman, Andrew (Box 21)
    - Faculty Meeting, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00009; Soren (Box 21)
    - Islamic Center; Provost's House, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00010; Chapman, Andrew (Box 21)
    - Homecoming Banner Making, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00011; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Dean Reitman, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00012; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Homecoming Pep Rally, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00013; Wong, Sarah (Box 21)
    - Homecoming, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00002.00014; Will (Box 21)
    - The Cannon, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00015; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Tufts Music Department, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00016; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Speech 9/11 - Serge Schmemann, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00002.00017; Burns, Soren (Box 21)
    - Christine Economos (Nutrition Professor), 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00018; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Tufts Police, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00019; Walters, Megan (Box 21)
    - Olin College, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00020; Aguilar, Veronica (Box 21)
    - Pool; Health Services, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00002.00021; Chapman, Andrew (Box 21)
    - Anti-war Protest, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00022; Hendrickson (Box 21)
    - Car Crash, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00002.00023; Aguilar, Veronica (Box 21)
    - Candle Lighting Ceremony, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00002.00024; Kantor, Max Felker (Box 21)
      Date from binder, Note inlcuded
    - Candle Lighting Ceremony, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00002.00025; Kantor, Max Felker (Box 21)
      Attached to above negative
    - Co-ed Dorms; Take Back the Night, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00002.00026; Chapman, Andrew (Box 21)
    - Vonnegut Ticket Line, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00027; Bedoya, A. (Box 21)
    - Bilingual Education vs. Immersion, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00028; Wong, Sarah (Box 21)
    - Kurt Vonnegut, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00029; Wittels (Box 21)
    - Kurt Vonnegut, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00030; Wittels (Box 21)
    - Iraq Teach-in (news), 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00031; Wong, Sarah (Box 21)
    - Harris St. Fire, 2002 -- 2004; UA176.002.021.00002.00032; Wittels, Will (Box 21)
      Film form included, Date from binder
    - Red Bones Fire, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00033; Wittels, Will (Box 21)
    - Bush Speech, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00034; Soren (Box 21)
    - War Protests in Davis, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00035; Soren (Box 21)
    - Major Week, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00036; Chester, Penelope (Box 21)
    - Classroom Renovations, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00037; Chester, Penelope (Box 21)
    - Margery Davies Bias Intervention, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00038; Odashima, Kay (Box 21)
    - Medford City Council, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00039; Wittels, Will (Box 21)
    - INS Dissolution, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00040; Burns, Katharine (Box 21)
    - Downtown Crossing, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00041; Churella, Andrew (Box 21)
    - Peace Rally, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00042; Chester (Box 21)
      Information sheet attached
    - Music Building, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00043; Chester, Penelope (Box 21)
    - Dennis Hale (Speech about Israel), 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00044; Chester, Penelope (Box 21)
    - Field Hockey, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00045; Burns, Soren (Box 21)
    - Field Hockey, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00046; Burns, Soren (Box 21)
    - Miles Lerner, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00047; Carre, Ray (Box 21)
      Date from binder, information sheet attached
    - Alumni Association Senior Awards Dinner, 2002; UA176.002.021.00002.00048; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 21)
    - Taskforce on the Undergrad, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00049; Chester, Penelope (Box 21)
    - Tisch Library, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00050; Chester, Penelope (Box 21)
    - Tuftonia's Day, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00051; Chester, Penelope (Box 21)
    - Saudi Ambassador, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00052; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - Saudi Ambassador, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00053; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - Saudi Ambassador, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00054; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - Saudi Ambassador, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00055; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - Dean Day: Steve Grossman, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00056; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - 123: Smoking Bars in Davis, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00057; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 21)
    - Tuition Increase, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00058; DeBoer, Danny (Box 21)
    - Head of the Charles: Fletcher 70th Anniversary, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00059; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 21)
    - Parent's Day Weekend, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00060; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 21)
    - Admissions: Tisch: Olin Center: TUPD, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00061; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 21)
    - Community Day: Ben Cohen, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00062; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - Coming Out Day Rally, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00063; Singhal, Rashmi (Box 21)
    - Kaleidoscope: Hazel Bright: Awad Halibi: Marilyn Glater, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00064; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 21)
    - Robert Kraft Awards, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00065; O'Brien, Kelly (Box 21)
    - Daniel Dennett, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00066; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 21)
    - Communications Networking Night: Alumni House, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00067; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - TCUJ, 2003; UA176.002.021.00002.00068; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
  - Men's S, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003
    - North Station T Stop, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00001; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - Fraternity/Sorority Rush, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00002; Beck, Casey (Box 21)
    - Police Beat, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00003; Beck, Casey (Box 21)
    - Virgin Mary: Sacred Heart Church, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00004; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - EPIIC Symposium, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00005; Beck, Casey (Box 21)
    - Food Poisoning in Campus Food, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00006; Beck, Casey (Box 21)
    - International Day of Reflection- Candlelight Vigil, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00007; Beck, Casey (Box 21)
    - Alderman Meeting, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00008; Loeb, Brian (Box 21)
      Film form included, attached to UA176/002-021.00003.00009
    - Alderman Meeting, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00009; Loeb, Brian (Box 21)
      Film form included, attached to UA176/002-021.00003.00008
    - Medical Center, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00010; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
    - Israeli Ambassador, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00011; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
      Film form included, attached to UA176/002-021.00003.00012 and UA176/002-021.00003.00013
    - Israeli Ambassador, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00012; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
      Film form included attatched to UA176/002-021.00003.00011 and UA176/002-021.00003.00013
    - Israeli Ambassador, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00013; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
      Film form included attatched to UA176/002-021.00003.00011 and UA176/002-021.00003.00012
    - March for Women's Lives: TPAN Senior Awards, 2004; UA176.002.021.00003.00014; Adams, Ford (Box 21)
      Film form included attatched to UA176/002-021.00003.00015 and UA176/002-021.00003.00016